(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-04T12:30:28.982408",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
おはのじゃー！あいさつしますのじゃー！
Good morning, naja! Time for my greeting, naja!
初配信！遊びまわりたい！ご利益担当の式神だよ～！
First stream! I want to play around! I'm the Shikigami of good fortune!
あちちめらなのじゃー！
I'm Achichi Mera, naja!
めっちゃいい曲かかった！
Such a great song just started playing!
今日は遊びまわりたい歌枠リレーですのじゃー！
Today is the "I Want to Play Around" singing relay, naja!
簡単に今日の流れをおぬさらに紹介しますのじゃー！
Let me briefly introduce today's schedule to you all, naja!
えー、20時からわし、あちちめら、20時20分からそらちなそぴあ、20時40分から鈴鳴つづり、
Um, starting at 20:00 is me, Achichi Mera; at 20:20, Sorachina Sophia; at 20:40, Suzuna Tsuzuri;
21時から100堂京香、それぞれ個人の枠で歌を歌いまして、そして最後に21時20分、あちちめらチャンネルで全員集合コラボを行いますのじゃー！
and at 21:00, 100-do Kyoko. Each of us will sing on our individual channels, and finally at 21:20, we'll have a full-group collaboration on the Achichi Mera channel, naja!
今日のおぬらの予定決まったの、初配信順にしてみたのじゃー！
I decided on everyone's schedule today by the order of our debut streams, naja!
今日のイベントの話とかも4人コラボの時にできたらいいなって思ってるので、早速わしからお歌歌っていこうかの！1人20分じゃからね、わしがねゆっくりしゃべってたらね、あの、あとね、あの、みんなが歌えなくなっちゃうから歌っていこうと思いますのじゃー！
I thought it'd be nice to talk about today's event during the 4-person collab, so I'll start singing right away, naja! Each person gets 20 minutes, so if I talk too slowly, the others won't get to sing. That's why I'm going to start singing now, naja!
おぬら全員のチャンネル登録と高評価をお忘れなくお願いしますのじゃー！
Don't forget to subscribe to everyone's channels and give us lots of likes, naja!
今日はのお題になし、あの、ジラしなし、なぜなら時間がパツパツじゃから！
Today there's no prompt, no teasing, because time is super tight!
ということで早速最初の曲、よいしょ！
With that said, let's get right into the first song, yoisho!
最初の曲はこちら！おぬら聴きたかったじゃろ？聴きたかったじゃろ？
The first song is this one! You wanted to hear it, didn't you? You wanted to hear it, right?
わしが最初の歌ってみたで歌うかって結構予想されてた、サラマンダーという曲を歌わせて
A lot of people predicted I'd sing "Salamander" for my very first cover song...
いただきますのじゃー！ちょっと緊張するけど、頑張る！頑張る！緊張するのじゃー！行くのじゃー！
Let me sing it, naja! I'm a bit nervous, but I'll do my best! I'm so nervous, naja! Here we go, naja!
サラマンダー ああ ホットが良くない やっぱばばばば大問題？
Salamander, ah, isn't it hot? Is it a huge problem, yappababababa?
ねぇだっては 良くなくない？もっとがききたい 頭の中は最高更新中
Hey, isn't it not good? I want more, my mind is currently updating its record!
サラマンダー たったと中
Salamander, tatta to chuu
いっぱい欲しい クセになるなんてずるいじゃない？
Wanting so much, getting addicted is unfair, isn't it?
えい 知ってたんなら 先に伝えといってほしいかな
Hey, if you knew, you should've told me beforehand!
ねぇ もう参戦です ハマっちゃって きみなしじゃダメ ダメなっちゃって
Hey, I've already joined the battle, got hooked, without you I'm no good, getting useless,
リピっちゃいたい ピリっちゃいたい おかわりできるかな
I want to repeat it, I want a spicy kick, can I have seconds?
もう1回 サラマンダー ああ ホットが良くない やっぱばばばば大問題？ねぇだっては良く…
Once more, Salamander, ah, isn't it hot? Is it a huge problem, yappababababa? Hey, isn't it...
ねぇ、だてには良くない？
Hey, isn't it no good?
もっとが聞きたい
I want to hear more.
頭の中は最高更新中
My mind is constantly updating its best.
やめられないのよ
I can't stop.
やめたくないのよ
I don't want to stop.
ちゃんとふうして
Blow on it properly...
火傷したくないなら
if you don't want to get burned.
緊張するのじゃ
I'm getting nervous.
いっぱい汗 よだれとかばっちり止まらない
Sweating buckets, drooling endlessly, won't stop at all.
何回だってメラメラになって仕上がりたい
No matter how many times, I want to blaze up and finish strong.
生き急いじゃってあっちっち ちょい猫舌だからめんどくさい
Living too fast, it's scorching hot, I have a sensitive tongue so it's a pain.
リピっちゃいたい ピリっちゃいたい おかわりできるかな もう１回
I want to replay it, I want it spicy, can I get seconds? One more time!
真っ赤に燃えてみたい
I want to burn bright red.
燃えたいのじゃ
I want to burn.
サラマンダー
Salamander!
ねぇ、だてには良くない？
Hey, isn't it no good?
もっとが聞きたい
I want to hear more.
頭の中は最高更新中
My mind is constantly updating its best.
サラマンダー
Salamander!
ほっくにだめじゃ やっぱぱぱぱぱ絶好調？
It's no good in my cheek, or maybe nope nope nope, in top form?
ねぇ、正直なくなくない？
Hey, honestly, isn't it true?
本音が聞きたい
I want to hear your true feelings.
頭の中は最高更新中
My mind is constantly updating its best.
やめられないのよ
I can't stop.
やめたくないのよ
I don't want to stop.
ちゃんとふうして
Blow on it properly...
火傷したくないなら
if you don't want to get burned.
抜け出したいけど
I want to break out, but...
抜け出せないのよ
I can't break out.
ちゃんとふうして 火傷したくないなら
Blow on it properly if you don't want to get burned.
ちゃっちゃっ
Cha cha!
サラマンダーでしたのじゃ
That was Salamander!
お主ら聞きたかったでしょ？DECO*27さんのね「サラマンダー」って曲。
You guys wanted to hear it, right? DECO*27-san's song "Salamander".
プロセカとカップヌードルコラボの曲じゃったかな？
Was it a collaboration song with Project SEKAI and Cup Noodle?
うん、聞きたかった？聞きたかった？
Yeah, did you want to hear it? Did you want to hear it?
「やったー！」とか「あっちっち」とか言ってるしの。
You were saying "Yay!" and "Hot hot!" and stuff.
いやぁ、トップパタ緊張するー！
Man, being first is so nerve-wracking!
緊張するけど、よいしょ。
It's nerve-wracking, but alright.
次の曲歌うのじゃ。もうね、歌枠リレーとはね
Time to sing the next song. You know, with a singing relay,
たくさん歌うもの。よいしょ。
there are so many songs to sing. Alright.
次の曲はこちら！アニソンも持ってきましたのじゃ！
The next song is this! I brought an anisong too!
「とどめィン♥レシピ」というアニソンを、持ってきましたのじゃ！
I brought an anisong called "Todomein Recipe"!
これ、これを...えっと、あ、全部でわし4曲歌う、わし4曲歌います！
This, this... um, ah, in total I'm singing 4 songs, I'll sing 4 songs!
行くのじゃ！え、大丈夫かな？こんなゆっくりしてて大丈夫かな？
Let's go! Eh, will it be okay? Is it okay to be this slow?
ちょ、ゆっくりすぎる？あ、BGM
Ah, is it too slow? Ah, BGM...
歌うのじゃ！
Time to sing!
初めて聴くお主も、きっと好きになると思いますのじゃ！
Even those of you hearing it for the first time will definitely grow to love it!
ふぅふぅらったったったったふぅふぅらったったったっぱ、えい！えい！
Fuu fuu rattattatta fuu fuu rattattatta, hei! hei!
ラったったったったふぅふぅえい！
Rattattatta fuu fuu hei!
どんな味が好きとか、何が食べられないとか
What kind of flavors do you like, what can't you eat...
知っといた方がいいかなってね
It's probably better to know those things, right?
ため息混じりに寝る お菓子と妄想のレシピの中に
Mixed with sighs, sleeping amidst a recipe of sweets and delusions,
恋心入っちゃった
a little bit of love crept right in.
シフォンケーキにカスタード スコーンにクロテッドクリーム
Chiffon cake, custard, scones and clotted cream,
だけどやっぱそれっておかしいわ どうして私なんだろ
but still, isn't that strange? Why does it have to be me?
急にそんなこと言い出して ああどうしよう
Suddenly saying things like that, ah, what should I do?
君を好きになっちゃうかなんて 分からないけど
I don't know if I'll end up falling in love with you,
大切な人だなんて ああ照れくさいかな
but calling you someone precious feels kind of embarrassing.
君は真面目なトーンで 好きなんて言ってでしょ
You say you like me in such a serious tone,
ちょっとドキッとしちゃうじゃん なんて非日常的な
making my heart skip a beat—how extraordinary is that?
レボリューション
Revolution!
ラったったったったふぅふぅえい！
Rattattatta fuu fuu hei!
どんな味が好きとか、何が食べられないとか
What kind of flavors do you like, what can't you eat...
知っといた方がいいかなってね
It's probably better to know those things, right?
ため息混じりに寝る お菓子と妄想のレシピの中に
Mixed with sighs, sleeping amidst a recipe of sweets and delusions,
戸惑いが入っちゃった
a little bit of love crept right in.
プリンアームロ生クリーム ときめくチョコレートモンブラン
Pudding, whipped cream, heart-throbbing chocolate, mont blanc...
だけどやっぱ これって おかしいの
But still, isn't this weird?
どうして 私 赤いの
Why am I so red?
あの言葉を 思い出して
Remembering those words...
もうどうしよ 君が 好きって言ったって
What should I do? You said you liked me,
どうしていいか 分かんないよ
But I don't know what to do.
秘密って言っても 否定されたら ちょっとショック
Even if it's a secret, denial is a bit of a shock.
君に思い切ってさ 「ねえ、あの」って呼び止めちゃった
So I boldly stopped you and said, "Hey, um..."
ちょっとドキッとしちゃうじゃん 急に笑顔なんてしないでよ
My heart skips a beat—don't suddenly smile like that!
Everybody let me GO!!
It's a show Time Now!! Everybody let's GO!!
Go Fight Win!! let me show me make me down!!
Go Love Win!! take my heart Everybody
let me GO!! It's a show Time Now!!
Everybody let's GO!! Go Fight Win!!
let me show me make me down!! Go Love Win!!
GO GO GO GO GO!!
のじゃあ…
Noja...
のじゃあ のじゃあ のじゃあ
Noja, noja, noja...
君のその無表情の中に
Within your expressionless face,
時々見た笑顔とかがっかりとかあれ探してるの…?
I sometimes search for a smile or disappointment...?
君に思い切ってさ 「ねえ、あの」って呼び止めちゃった
So I boldly stopped you and said, "Hey, um..."
ちょっとドキッとしちゃうじゃん 急に笑顔なんてしないでよ
My heart skips a beat—don't suddenly smile like that!
君を好きになっちゃうなんてわからないけど
I don't know if I'll end up falling for you,
大切な人だなんて照れくさいかな
But calling you someone special might be embarrassing.
君は真面目なトーンで「好き」なんて言ってしょっ中
In a serious tone, you said "I like you" so often—
なんて非日常的なレボリューション
What an extraordinary revolution!
恋のレシピだっ
It's the recipe for love!
ったった らったったっ ふうふう ったった らっぱ イェイ イェイ
(Scatting)
ったった らったったっ ふうふう ったった らっぱ イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ
ひとりで歌うの大変じゃった
It was hard singing alone!
かわいかった?
Was it cute?
そうじゃわ サラマンダーってこんな可愛い曲なんじゃよ
"Salamander" is such a cute song, you know!
ありがとのじゃあ とまどいレシピでしたのじゃあ
Thank you, that was "Tomadoi Recipe".
もう一曲 ボーカロイド曲おまちしましたのじゃ
I've prepared another Vocaloid song!
次が3曲目
Next is the third song.
お水飲むのじゃ
Time to drink some water.
落ち着いたから
Now that I've calmed down,
キャットラビングっていう曲を歌いますのじゃ
I'll sing a song called "Cat Loving".
早速行くのじゃ
Let's go right ahead!
痛いことは嫌いですか
Do you hate painful things?
君の手の平は嫌いじゃない
I don't hate the palm of your hand.
言葉は雨ダマみたいに甘く広がってココロ満たす
Words are like candy drops, spreading sweetly to fill my heart.
ああ全然わかってない永遠に言う通り
Ah, you totally don't get it, doing as you're told forever.
(どこにいても)鳴呼「何で？」は聞いてない
No matter where you are, ah, "Why?" wasn't asked.
もっともっとあの子みたいに可愛くならなくちゃ
I have to become cuter, more and more like that girl.
愛情は染めに色はハメにもう大体大体のってわかんなくなる
Affection is dyeing, color is fitting, already I don't understand most things.
延命またたび主にご褒美もう夜のって話されないように
Prolonging life, matatabi, master's reward, so I won't be let go tonight.
今日だってちゃんと言いしょの毛づくろいにゃんていこうにするから愛して
Today too, I'll secretly groom myself and make it purrfect, so love me.
Everybody Today it's rubbing day!
Get it Get it This is my courtship
Any Any Any time is fine with me Gimme Gimme
Love me, my darling
会いたいわ間違いなんて皆は言う取り付かれているって
If everyone says wanting to meet you is a mistake, being possessed...
ならこの胸でうずく締め付けるような切なさは何なの？
What is this tightness constricting my chest?
あんなの選ぶ言葉 とまどう指先
Choosing something like that, hesitating fingertips,
倒せぬ横顔 あらんだむごきぎ
a face that cannot be defeated, random movements.
もしかして今日は優しくなれてくれるのかな
Could it be that today you'll learn to be gentle with me?
君のそれが耐えられるの紹介で
In the introduction where I can endure that of yours,
私だけなんだよね
it's only me, right?
あからさまにからとまさらに もうやだってもう離れられないよね
Openly, saying "I hate this" and yet we can't bear to part,
そうだよね
right?
感情は徐々に舞台はさらに もう Lieも嘘のように転がせばいい
Emotions gradually, the stage even more, just roll 'em over like lies.
柑橘の匂いだって凌ぐのだ もう噛んだって叱られるだけだし
Surviving citrus scents, even if I bite now, I'll just get scolded.
今日だってちゃんとお座敷で大人しく にゃんってお好きなように完全討伐して
Sitting properly on the tatami, subjugating completely just as you like!
キャットラミングでしたのじゃ
That was Cat Laming!
猫ちゃんなのじゃ にゃーお
I'm a kitty cat, Nya~o!
メラ！
Mela!
あちちメラなのだんな
Hot hot Mela, darling!
最後の曲
The last song,
メラ！
Mela!
歌いますのじゃ！
I will sing it!
今なんじゃない? メラメラとたぎれ
Isn't this the moment? Blaze up and surge,
眠っているだけの正義
the justice that's just lying dormant.
こんな僕も君のヒーローになりたいのさ
Even a guy like me wants to become your hero!
かっこいい君には ぼくじゃ頼りないのかななんて
Thinking I might not be reliable enough for someone as cool as you,
そりゃそうだよなって だって 今もこうして迷ってる
well, of course that's true, since I'm still hesitating like this.
手を取ってくれないか
Won't you take my hand?
ギフトとテイクさ 君が僕のヒーローだったように
It's give and take, just like you were my hero.
今なんじゃない? メラメラとたぎれ
Isn't this the moment? Blaze up and surge,
こんな僕にもひそむ正義がどうしようもない
the justice lurking inside a guy like me can't be helped—
衝動にかられて ほら気付けば手を握っている 一体全体
driven by impulse, before I knew it, I'm holding your hand.
そんなに荷物を背負い込んでどこへ行くの
Carrying so much luggage on your back, where are you going?
ねぇねぇ待って僕にちょっと預けてみては
Hey, wait, why don't you leave a bit of it with me?
信じてばかりの僕と 信じることが怖い君と
Between me who keeps believing and you who are afraid to trust,
どちらが正しいのかなんて
wondering which of us is right...
誰にも分からないさ
nobody knows that.
僕だけの世界 ギフトとテイクさ
Our own world, it's give and take.
補い合えたあか抜けには 同じ夢を見たい
On nights when we make up for each other, I want to dream the same dream.
君はかっこいいと 苦しめて一人ぼっちにさせたのは
If calling you cool and leaving you all alone was somehow my fault,
少し僕のせいなんだよな ごめんね
I'm sorry.
だけど見るべきはリアルだ 今こそ僕が救うんだ
But what we need to look at is reality, and right now I will save you!
抱かないで信じて頼ってほしいんだ
Don't hold back, believe in me, I want you to rely on me.
今なんじゃない? メラメラとたぎれ
Isn't this the moment? Blaze up and surge,
こんな僕にもひそむ正義がどうしようもない
the justice lurking inside a guy like me can't be helped—
衝動にかられて ほら気付けば手を握っている ほっとけない
driven by impulse, before I knew it, I'm holding your hand, I can't leave you be.
そんなに荷物を背負い込んでどこへ行くの
Carrying so much luggage on your back, where are you going?
ほんのちょっと 僕にちょっと預けてみては
Hey, why don't you leave just a little bit of it with me?
ぼくにちょっと預けてみては
Why don't you entrust it to me a little?
ああ
Ah...
こんな僕も君のヒーローになりたいのさ
Even someone like me wants to be your hero.
もうすぐ20分なので、この曲でおしまいですよじゃ！
It's almost 20 minutes, so this is our final song!
お主ら、4曲歌っちめらの歌を聴いてくれてありがとうなのじゃあ！
Thanks for listening to Achichimela's four songs!
じゃん！
Ta-da!
ありがとうございましたなのじゃ！
Thank you very much!
これで歌っちめらの歌枠はおしまい！4人コラボでも歌いますのじゃ！
That wraps up Achichimela's singing stream! We'll also sing in a 4-person collab!
次はソピア！
Next is Sophia!
それではお主らさらばじゃ！
So see you guys later!